Help ...
I need help .
Pee Mak
Tis been 'th a long time 'th
and still no help 'th hast come to our rescue .
Thee enemy hast surrounded us and break 'th our lines .
Our forces
hast take 'th heavy casualties and thus dying in droves .
If this keep 'th up 'th
I think 'th
we will definitely be defeat 'th .
Why the hell are you talking like that ?
So lame . Are you from the dark ages ? !
Private Mark is injured .
Hey Mark !
Ouch ...
doc ?
You 'll be okay .
You just sprained your leg .
Sprained my leg ? !
Damn !
You moan
like you 're in heat !
Am I going to make it back home to Phrakhanong ?
my wife probably gave birth already .
This can 't be the end of the line for us ?
Damn it !
Don 't give up !
Remember " 300 " The Battle of Thermopylae ?
King Leonidas
Stelios
They were all outnumberd and outgunned .
Hmmmmm
right ?
Oh
Sorry
I never got to the end .
Then think of " Rocky
Rocky Road ?
It 's yummy ! Where is it ?
Where is it ?
Gosh
How about the " Last Samurai
he fought so hard his blade shattered .
He didn 't even think of giving up .
Here we still have our swords
all our arms and legs .
Asshole !
Sorry ! Sorry !
Just all our swords then .
Do we not have a fighting chance ?
Yeah !
Kill them !
Shit
They 've got guns . I forgot .
Ouch ..
Mark ?
Hey Shin
since we are all going to die anyways .
Can I ask you something ?
What 's with the hair ?
When I was little there was a bubonic plague outbreak .
I almost died .
So my mother swore to God if I survived
I would keep this hairdo for the rest of my life .
I rather die than live with that ugly topknot hairdo .
Look like a dog 's ankle bunion .
What about yours ?
I 'm a trend setter .
Stop shooting already !
do you have any last words ?
No I don 't .
No matter what I will make it back to see my wife and baby .
I will not allow myself to die here .
Nor will all of you .
Pee Mak ...
Why did you come out ? Go inside . Hurry .
Too many people playing . I won 't deal you in .
Why not .
no play .
Get on with it .
Are you going to shuffle until dawn ?
Why don 't you go put on a card show .
Is your dad David Blaine ?
Hurry up . Come on .
Hey what 's this ?
A Natural 9
Shit ! I got 0
pay UP -
What 's wrong ?
The wound hurts ?
I am fine .
I can 't believe that you survived .
Man you must be invincible .
I am grateful to all of you for bringing me back here .
We are the one who should be grateful .
we would be dead already .
Actually you should pronounce my name as ...
MARK " with the K in the end .
Huh ?
M arrrrk ?
Forget it . Just call me " Mak " then .
The only person who calls me " Mark " is my daddy .
But he 's back to the United States of America with the missionaries .
Everyone in my village calls me Mak .
WTF ?
Hey guys we made it to Phrakhanong .
We 're here ?
Finally .
Where is everybody ?
Thank you .
You 're welcome
Nak
Nak honey
I 'm back .
Nak
ls Nak taking a dump ?
Hey Nak
Where were you ?
I was really worried .
I thought I would never see you again .
Don 't cry baby .
You won 't look handsome .
You know
when I was at war
I missed you so much .
I missed you a lot .
I missed you soooo much !
I missed you more than anyone in whole world .
Mak is whipped !
did you miss me at all ?
No
Why not ?
You don 't love me anymore ?
You crazy .
I do .
You 're mean .
Don 't joke like that .
Isn 't that special ?
what about our baby ?
He 's playing over there .
Where ? Let daddy see .
Wow he is handsome just like his daddy .
You know I gave him your favorite name .
Nak ?
Dang
my boy . ) ' -
What 's so cool about the name Dang ?
Go figure .
My servant has a cooler name .
Hey you GUYS
Nak .
Hello there .
these are my friends
This is Aey
Puak and that 's Shin .
And what 're you guys going to do now ?
I guess tonight will be difficult to find a boat .
We will stay here for a night .
Why just one night ?
You all can stay here until the war is over .
The house opposite to us has been empty since my aunty passed away .
There 's a boat for you to use too .
Geez
His aunt won 't haunt us ?
She will haunt you until your hair falls out .
We will stay here for a night . Don 't want to be a bother .
Hey
They are welcoming us and you just turn them down ?
Aey .
Right ?
Mak 's wife is so damn beautiful .
Hey ... Careful that 's our friend 's wife .
You know I am a bad soldier .
How come ?
When I was at war
I never thought of Siam
my country .
All I thought about was you .
This soldier should be executed by a firing squad .
Yes
You should be .
You know
I waited for you at the pier every day .
I am here now .
I promise you
I won 't go anywhere anymore .
Hey
Nak
our house has fireflies too ?
Wow so beautiful .
That 's a Krasue ghost .
What ?
Nak
Why are you joking with me like that ?
You know I am really scared of ghosts .
What are you looking for ?
I will wear my Buddha amulet .
The doctor took it off when they bandaged me .
Gosh
There 's a lot of blood on it . Just put it away for now
and I will clean it later .
Okay
My wife is the nicest person in Siam .
And you smell great too .
At this temple ...
There are
seven palm trees .
The Hill Myna is out
but has not returned .
Chirping
Hey guys look . They aren 't scared of people .
Cute huh .
Yeah . So cute .
Cute my ass ! Damn .
Why do you have to be animal lover this early ! Can 't you see we are all still trying to sleep ?
How can anybody sleep with you chirping .
go eat somewhere else .
Go away . Fly away out of my house .
Hey ! Wake up you guys .
You 're here early .
Any later the market will close .
What 's on the boat ?
The bodies of soldier who died in the war .
The cemetery is all full .
So we must return the bodies back to their families
for burial .
Hey
keep rowing .
Geez .
Snakehead fish .
Fresh ! Small and big . We have it .
Wow
Today the market is very crowded .
Hello .
Snacks and desserts ?
We got cookies too .
Aunty Nim
May I have 2 cookies and 2 of those snacks ?
Mak . Yes ?
We 're all out !
Damn it . We won 't get to eat any .
Uncle Aum . Uncle Aum .
Mak I want to buy some fish for Nak .
Not for sale . Today 's a Buddhist holy day . I am releasing them .
Sathu . Go go go .
Don 't be in the way .
Do you think that 's a merit ?
What got into him ?
Liquor shop
Aunty Priek ... Aunty Priek
Wake up . You have customers .
Aunty Priek
You don 't remember me ?
I can do ?
No
Gosh
How many staffs do you think we need for a small liquor store ?
You think I need salesperson ? Mixologist ?
Waitress ?
Hostess ?
Bartender ? Dishwasher ? Bus boy ?
I got them all .
Please drink up .
She 's even got an escort .
Very good .
You look familiar .
I am Mak .
I just got back from the war .
I 'd probably hit on you .
You are looking good .
As pretty as your ghost !
You really don 't know Mak ?
If you want to know
Bend down and look between the legs and you 'll see that Nak and your kid are ...
Mom
Shush Ping
You 're drunk . Go rest . Mom lam not drunk .
Why won 't you let me go ? I 'm not drunk .
Go . Get up .
I 'm sorry . When she is drunk she talks nonsense .
Get inside . Nak ! Nak !
Nak ! Let her come . I 'm not scared !
Nak ... Let her come .
What 's wrong with her ?
don 't you think ?
Yeah . What did aunty Priek mean anyway ?
Why do you have to look between the legs ?
Yoga exercise ?
My mom once told me
if you look between the legs
you can tell if they 're ghosts .
You mean ...
Nak is a ghost ?
That 's crazy
She 's too hot to be a ghost .
Right . Beautiful like that
Even if she is a ghost I would still have her .
Why did Aunty Priek talk to Mak like that ?
Because she was wasted .
So everything she says is nonsense .
Where the heck is Mak ?
How come he isn 't here drinking with us ?
Aey
you 're spilling all the booze .
You go and get Mak here .
Hurry UP -
Why me ?
Because you drank the least .
It 's been over an hour and you can 't even down one glass .
That 's right .
We are all drunk . So just go .
Oops my bad .
Hey don 't waste it . Hurry up .
Mak !
is Mak here ?
Hey Shin .
Nak .
Is Mak here ?
He 's sleeping .
I will wake him for you .
Please come in first .
Where is Dang ?
Nak
are you ok ?
You ran out of coconut husks ?
Shin ! What the heck is wrong with you ?
Puak . Slap me please ?
That 's hard .
You told me to .
Where the heck is Mak ?
How come he isn 't here drinking with us ?
Gosh Aey
You 're spilling all the booze .
Shit . Déjà vu .
What do you mean déjà vu ?
You go and get Mak here . Hurry up .
why me ?
What are you scared of ?
then seduce her .
There 's no such things as ghosts .
You want to bet ?
You won 't get me this time .
The drums of war sound off like rolling thunder as we set out to protect our homeland .
Our thirst for battle is great even though there are no elephants ride .
Dusk fills my emptiness with thoughts of love for my beautiful dearest .
Roused to the point of release I raise my white flag in sweet surrender .
I bust a rag out and just polish the sword . Yay !
Shin ?
Where is Mak ? Nak is a ghost !
Nak is really a ghost !
What are you babbling about ?
go vomit somewhere else .
Seriously . I went up to Mak 's house .
His house looks run-down and abandoned .
Maybe Nak is feeling lazy . But the crib was swinging by itself .
Maybe there 's a strong breeze . You are imagining things .
I wasn 't !
I saw Nak upstairs
but she was able to reach to the ground to grab a lime .
Maybe one of her arms is longer than the other ?
Didn 't you know our arms are not exactly the same length ?
Look at mine . See ? Not the same .
Or maybe Nak was just using a stick to pick it up .
You 're drunk and your imagination get the best of you .
Hey do you remember our marching song ?
Let 's dance . Ready .
The drums of war sound off like rolling thunder as we set out to protect our homeland .
Our thirst for battle is great even though there are no elephants ride .
Dusk fills my emptiness with thoughts of love for my beautiful dearest .
Mak
Can 't we sleep a bit longer ?
Come on . Help me .
I don 't know what 's going with the townsfolk .
Only you guys are willing to help .
Hey Shin .
Aren 't you done freaking out ?
get up and help us .
Yeah Ter
go get the axe and help Puak .
Ask Nak where the axe is .
What again ?
I went up to Mak 's house . The house looks run-down and abandoned .
My mom once told me
if you look between the legs
you can tell if they 're ghosts .
Hmmm I am ...
looking for an axe . Do you know where it is ?
Shin .
I didn 't see shit .
So stop freaking out .
Really ? Yes .
How is that possible ?
Oh gosh
Shit !
Damn I 'm not even finished yet .
Holy shit !
Ouch .
Shit I saw a # $ " * @ %
Hey Ter . What happened to your face ?
I saw a # $ " * # @ *
What ?
There 's a " # " $ # " % @
What the heck is he talking about ?
Thank you .
Oh my ...
Nak is a " / ' \ # * @ !
What are you talking about ?
Nak
is
a
What am I ?
Ter ?
Hey did you get stung by bees ?
My mom told me to use limestone paste to heal it .
can you make some ?
Let me see .
Thank you .
Mind your step .
Nak is @ " # * " $
I saw a % # @ behind the house .
She really is % @ # %
stop being silly .
What are you saying ?
I cannot understand .
Nak is a ghost .
it 's raining just get inside .
Ter
What happened to your face ?
What paper is that ?
! ? ee ? ing ( Bee sting )
Let me see . See what ?
The paper .
What paper ? I don 't have any .
Ter .
! ? ee ? ing
I want to look at the paper . ! ? ee ? ing
Let me see it now .
Ter
I @ I \ * * AA ! # @ ^ * # I \ * # $ A @ ^ * *
Oh he said " it 's about to rain . He has clothes drying outside . " He will go home now .
Puak how did you make sense of that .
I don 't know .
Let 's go already and get the damn clothes .
Gosh I almost had a fling with a ghost .
What are you doing ?
Packing my stuff and leave . We can 't stay here .
Ter ?
Of course . I saw it with my own eyes . The ruby ring is exactly like Nak 's .
Is the ruby big ?
Jerk . That 's not the point .
So how come when you looked between the legs you didn 't see anything ?
I don 't know . I looked between her legs and I saw nothing
except her hot pot .
What ?
I mean the pot in the kitchen .
Oh ok . You idiot !
You 're supposed to look between your own legs !
Oh really ?
And why didn 't you say so .
Huh ?
Do you think Mak can read ?
Of course . He looked really shock .
he went inside .
I know everything already .
Why didn 't you tell me .
Did you think I would be disgusted ?
Who told you ?
Who told me isn 't important .
We promise each other there wouldn 't be any secrets between us ?
I didn 't know how to tell you .
What if you couldn 't take it ?
I couldn 't risk it .
Why wouldn 't I take it ?
I used to be like that too .
why does he still look so in love ?
I know .
Shit ... I know why .
It says Nak is " gross " not a ghost !
If she is gross
then so what ?
But if you are really gross that 's disgusting .
You 've never had a under arm zit ? I had one last year and it was gross .
Sheez we 're wasting time .
Let 's pack up and get out of here .
Let 's go pack up now .
Hey why are you taking so long Ter ? Hurry .
I can 't abandon him .
What now ?
Are we really going to leave Mak with a ghost ?
Can I not go ?
NC )
You saw Nak with her long arm . So you go tell Mak .
How can someone that beautiful be a ghost ?
Anyone here ?
Anybody home ?
Hey Ping
Why are you crying ?
Can anyone help me slaughter my cow ?
I sympathize with you .
You must really love your cow .
But when you 're really starving you can eat anything . Don 't think too much .
I once ate my own dog . Not like that .
The cow is for a funeral offering .
Whose funeral ?
My mom .
Aunty Priek is dead ?
That day at the market .
When she told Mak about Nak . Nak was very angry and killed her .
Her body was found floating this morning .
Damn it .
Shin and Ter !
Mak
Hey
What 's up ?
Mak
I have something to tell you .
Do you know that
your wife is ...
Beautiful !
What ?
Oh yes I wanted to say that your wife is very good looking
Like Miss Universe .
I just couldn 't wait to tell you .
Wow you guys are so sweet .
You didn 't have to make it into big deal .
Oh no . We had to tell you now .
Next time there 's no need to rush .
My wife will still be pretty tomorrow .
See you .
Pee Mak
Why don 't you invite your friends to eat here ?
Hey make yourself at home . No need to be too formal .
Go ahead .
Everything is delicious .
Yeah .
I saw your mouth watering . So eat up .
We are full already .
Really ?
Yes . There was a buffet at the market .
Come on
Nak will be sad .
She worked so hard in the kitchen .
next time . Up to you
I will eat myself . You guys are missing out .
I shouldn 't have eaten so much .
On second thought we should have a bite .
Wow ! This dish looks good . I 'll try a bit .
Here you go .
Very nice . So delicious .
I told you .
You must try this one .
Huh ? Try this
Try it . Puak eat it .
Just try it . Eat up
Yeah just taste it .
Nak ?
Le Condon Bleu ?
why don 't you eat anything ?
Yeah Shin . This one is yours .
That is Nak 's signature dish .
Go for it Shin .
Yeah big bite .
How was it ?
Damn good !
My Nak is the best cook .
Hey anyone wants to hold Dang ?
My Dang . My son .
Peekaboo ! What 's up baby ?
Want to play with uncle Shin ?
Oh yeah Shin . You love kids .
Let 's play with uncle Shin .
Here we go .
My boy .
Dang really likes you .
Kiss me uncle Shin .
come to daddy .
What are you doing ?
Oh
I know
you guys
feel like playing charades ?
I like that idea .
please join us .
ok ?
Hurry up Shin .
Just watch me .
Throw ?
Javefin ?
Athlete ?
Throw ?
Throw away ?
Trout ?
No ?
What ?
Kitchen
Oh ... a cook ?
Beautiful cook ?
Damn what the hell ?
Nak 's kitchen ?
Mak 's kitchen .
No
Mak and Nak 's kitchen ?
No ?
Will he guess right in this life time ?
Pan ?
Knife ?
Spear ?
Correct ! I told you so !
What 's with the spear ?
Body ?
Armpit ?
Armpit hairs ?
No ! Sweaty armpit ?
Smelly armpit ?
No !
Bumpy armpits !
No that either !
Gosh !
I wonder what Mak 's IQ really is ?
a bed ?
right ?
Bamboo bed ?
Correct ! A spear near the bed ( danger nearby )
That 's right !
Yayyy ...
Who the heck came up with this phrase ?
Your dad must be Shakespeare . That one was difficult .
A bird ?
Fly ?
Bat ?
Shirt ? Correct !
Dog ?
Tongue ?
Dog tongue fish ?
Dog tongue fish wears a shirt ?
What the hell is it ?
what is it ?
Oh Nak ? No
Beautiful ?
Sexy ?
What ?
Woman ?
Wife ?
Oh I know
Dead
Dead-Shirt " ( Desert )
Correct !
Yayy ... - -'
Ter . This is a shirt and she is dead
pronounce as " Desert
that can 't be right .
right ?
Yeah Shin is wrong .
How can it be wrong ?
This is a shirt and she is dead ! So it 's " dead-shirt " ( Desert )
Yayy ... - -'
Something wrong with your brain !
What is going on ?
So what is the answer ?
Let me see the paper .
What are you doing Ter ?
I 'm still very hungry .
I better go check .
Yeah I was about to remind him too .
So let 's go before it burns . Quick quick .
How about the shirt ? Forget about it .
Why don 't you tell me the answer first ?
I already gave the right answer . Right my ass . That was close .
Hold on !
hurry up .
come on .
Wait up
Holy shit
hurry up .
Hey wait up
Ter hurry . Ter !
She 's right behind you
Omen Ter . Hurry up ' . !
untie the boat . Let 's go !
Paddle hard .
Why the heck are we turning ? !
Shit ! We 're back here again !
Go that way !
Why are you turning again ?
Where are you guys going in such a hurry ?
Don 't you want to finish the game ?
I didn 't get a chance to play yet .
So what phrase would you act out ?
NW OB
what does it mean ?
It means " Mind your own business ! " Did you even have to ask ?
Just go !
Damn it I think Nak is on to us for sure .
She won 't let us live .
What ?
You go check .
You guys get out of my house right now .
What 's wrong with you Mak ?
You guys are no different than the townsfolk
who think that my wife is a ghost .
You have to listen to us . Your wife died already .
Everybody knows it .
My wife is not dead .
Ping lied to all the villagers .
They said when I was at war
Ping tried to seduce Nak .
When I didn 't show any interest
he bad-mouthed me
by telling all kinds of lies .
Everyone believed him .
Now everybody hates Nak too .
I get the picture .
But you didn 't have to change your voice .
So that 's it .
So Ping fooled all of you too .
you 're the one who is being fooled .
Watch your mouth !
Stop being an idiot .
You have to believe us .
We are telling you this
because you are our friend .
I don 't need any friends like you !
Mak !
I think ...
we will really need to do something drastic .
I kicked them all out already .
What did your friends say ?
I don 't care what they say .
They cannot talk about you like that .
If you are really a ghost
then I should be able to see through you .
Let me try .
Hey
Hey I can see past you .
Wow
so cool !
Super cool .
Enough .
What did you do
to get this dirty ?
Let 's see what my darling prepared for me to eat .
Mmmm
your cooking is as good as always .
Nak my love are too pretty
to be a ghost . Right ?
Wait up !
A Ghost !
Why don 't you try to scare me ?
C 'mon stick your tongue out .
Scare me .
You are no fun . Boo !
don 't make me smack you upside the head .
Are you going to wear this mask all night ?
Why not ?
It 's kinda funny .
Okay .
looking far across the sky
the light is faint .
I know our time is coming to an end .
My heart is breaking but don 't know what else to do .
I want to cry ...
and beg time to go by slowly ... I need more time .
To look at each other . I wish I could freeze this moment ...
forever before we must part .
he won 't cry ?
Don 't worry
Dang doesn 't wake up in the middle of the night .
Look .
10 cents per ball .
you win a doll .
watch this .
I 'm just warming up .
This next one for sure .
Almost
This is the one .
Go
Yay !
Hit it .
Ouch
look fireworks .
Wow
See Nak
I told you . I have good aim . I will get you a doll .
Told you . Even as a kid I always had good aim .
The line is so long .
We 'll have to skip this ride .
Let 's go play something else ..
Look the line is gone .
You 're right .
Nak ...
Do you love me ?
What kind of question is that ?
Why ?
You don 't love me anymore ?
Of course I do .
Love me a lot ?
Lot lot
Love me a lot lot lot lot ?
there 's a haunted house too .
We can go after this .
Aren 't you scared of ghosts ?
me ?
Where ?
Come on out . Ghosts ? Nothing to be scared of .
Baby
If one day I die
can you live without me ?
Why are you asking me this ?
Just tell me . I want to know .
No
If anyone is going to die
then I want to die first .
If I don 't have you . I can 't go on .
But if I die first
you 'd be able to find a new husband easily
with that big butt of yours !
Haunted house .
Please keep the doll for me . Okay .
baby .
Gosh what kind of a ghost goes in a haunted house .
So who will be scaring who ?
I brought some powerful magic .
Like what ?
Holy rice . I got it from a monk .
Very sacred . Good good .
where is Aey ?
Where is he ?
Hey
Aey ?
I had diarrhea .
You were gone long .
don 't be scared .
Play with me . Play with me .
Boo !
I think I screamed too loud . So I scared him away .
Sorry Mak . This is for your own good .
Play with me . Shin you are the look out .
hold his legs .
It 's stuck .
Shit .
She 's on to us .
What are we going to do ? The door is stuck .
Gosh .
Too late . She is coming .
What now ?
I have no idea .
Hey
Why are you jumping ?
That damn boy did . He was so energetic .
Play with me .
Play with me . Play with me .
Or not .
UP to you .
You think Nak was fooled ?
Too many props .
What the hell ?
Hey !
You guys aren 't customers ?
Or did you get off work already ?
Why doesn 't anybody tell me ?
Damn it . Letting me hang upside down that long
might give me a stroke and kill me .
Ok let 's go home .
Go .
You over there . Time to go home .
The one who dressed up like Nak 's ghost .
Wow so trendy .
Are you new here ?
Let 's go home .
hurry !
Come on .
What the hell are you screaming for ?
It 's just a fake hand .
freaks me out . Look .
Hey untie him . Come on .
What is going on ?
Nak is really a ghost !
Not again . It 's all in your heads .
Just like this hand .
Mak come here .
What is it now ?
you scared me .
Holy Shit .
A lizard !
I thought you saw ...
Her !
There are otters around here ?
You guys won 't let this go .
We are telling you the truth .
If you don 't believe us try looking between the legs .
I did and saw nothing .
Maybe you didn 't do it right .
You have to look down between your own legs
not between Nak 's legs !
Of course .
Who would be that stupid !
My wife is not dead yet .
Hey Mak wait up .
Mak where are you going ?
How come he looked and didn 't see anything ?
Mak !
Mak ! Where are you ?
Shit
Is this Mak 's blood ?
Help !
is that you ?
Are you okay ?
Help me .
I 'm hurt .
Help me please .
Mak .
Help .
Help me .
Mak
what 's wrong ?
My wound .
Where ?
Gosh it 's bleeding out .
You 've had this wound for so long how come it 's not healed yet ?
Do you have something to pressure it ?
Shin
something isn 't right here ?
Yeah I know .
right ?
You idiot . Not about that !
About Mak looking down between his legs and not seeing anything .
So it means ...
Nak is still alive .
But the body I saw in the backyard
has the same ring as Nak 's .
come to think of it
The ring that I saw is on the ring finger of her left hand .
So what ?
It 's a wedding ring .
So that means
Mak should be wearing one too !
Softly
what are you doing ?
Damn Ter ! What the hell are you doing ? You 're hurting him !
Ter . Mak 's wound is still raw .
you scared me .
I thought you had your ring on .
My wedding ring ?
Well my hand hurts so I wear it around my neck instead .
These are the bodies of the soldier who went to war .
The cemetery is full now . So we have to return the bodies to their family to bury .
You 've had this wound for so long how come it 's not healed yet ?
No matter what I must return to see my wife and baby .
It 's him .
Run !
what the hell ?
What the hell ?
Wait for me .
What is happening ?
Shit ! The body I saw was Mak .
So Nak really is been bad-mouthed then .
What about when I saw Nak 's arm stretch all the way to the ground ?
Or ...
Maybe Nak used a long stick to get the lime .
Yeah must be that spear then .
Damn it .
Are you sure
that Nak is alive ?
So we must take her with us .
You really want to risk that ?
C 'mon .
How could we leave her like that ?
A woman all alone and so vulnerable .
I don 't care . No matter what ...
Nak and I will runaway together .
Huh ?
I mean runaway with us .
always thinking with the head in your pants . I can 't do this man .
Hey
But Puak does have a point .
Ter ?
If one day
Nak is haunted to death .
We are all partially to blame
for not lifting a finger to help .
The living cannot live with the dead !
Hurry
Nak
how are you ?
I 'm so sick of those villagers .
Idiots .
How could they believe Ping.l tried to talk to them but they wouldn 't listen .
Just now I busted more than a few lips on your behalf .
Please accept our apology .
Now we have no doubts about you being alive .
That 's okay .
Shin . What are you scared of now ?
Come here .
Here ...
Touch her . Trust me .
Come on .
You can actually touch her .
What ghost has skin that smooth ?
What about those dried leaves ?
Damn you .
She 's health conscious . How do you think she keeps up her nice figure .
Everyone eats organic foods now .
This is why she looks like a model .
But there were worms too .
Gosh
Organic means no insecticide so there are worms .
That 's how you tell it 's safe to eat .
You never studied about Hygiene in school ?
Where is Pee Mak ?
Hmmm
the war front has made its way here .
It 's very dangerous .
Mak told us to take you with us .
That 's right .
How come Pee Mak didn 't come with you ?
The way here is very difficult
So he is gathering rations and waiting at the waterfront .
Yeah
So let me get Dang for you .
Let 's get into the boat .
Come on Nak .
Not too far now . Mak should be around here .
Puak the boat is sinking !
Holy shit .
Too much weight . What should we do ?
Just toss what we don 't need .
Come on . Throw it Shin .
Hey sit still .
What now ? The water is getting inside the boat .
What else can we toss ?
Is Dang necessary ?
of course .
The paddles . Give me the paddles . Huh ?
Hand me the paddles now . Give them to me .
Here
Is that better ?
The boat is not sinking anymore !
It 's good the boat isn 't sinking anymore
stupid !
Why did you toss them out ?
They are so far now .
Should we swim to the other side ?
I can 't swim .
Shit. it 's Mak !
Pee Mak
Where are you going ?
leave us alone .
You 're dead . Just let us go .
What are you talking about ?
Mak died during the war . But he doesn 't know yet .
Nak . You can find a new boyfriend now .
Am I not right ?
What the hell is wrong with you all ?
Where are you taking my wife ? Pee Mak .
Let 's go .
Hurry .
Come on .
Pee Mak !
Pee Mak
Shit ! Where is he ? I don 't know .
Help . Help me .
Pee Mak !
can ghost drown ?
Don 't let him fool you .
Pee Mak
Help me . I have a muscle cramp
Pee Mak . He has cramps !
Help me . Ghost can have cramps ?
Please help him .
He must have taken an acting lesson .
Help me . His acting coach must be Ang Lee .
He 's not dead . Help him !
Mak !
Pee Mak
Calm down . Are you alright ?
What the heck ! Why did you run away from me ?
We thought you 're a ghost .
Why did you scream when we threw the holy rice at you ?
Gosh cuz they struck inside my wound .
you would scream too !
Shit ! We got the same problem again .
The boat is sinking .
right ?
he is .
Keep paddling .
Come on . Faster .
Come on !
Paddle . The boat is taking on water .
Hurry UP !
Wait .
Wait for what ?
The boat is sinking .
At first I thought Nak was a ghost and Mak was human .
Then it turned out Nak is human and Mak is a ghost .
just human .
So now who is the ghost and who is human ?
what the hell are you grumbling about ? Yeah ...
I was confused since the beginning of your sentence .
Nak Nak .
See ..
If Nak is still alive .
And Mak is still alive .
So whose body is it in the backyard ?
Aey ) '
why do you have the ring ?
Aey is a ghost !
Why is it when we realize something there is always flashes of lightning ?
who cares !
kick him overboard .
Hey come on . Let 's go .
The boat is taking on water . Let 's go .
Let 's go .
I am sorry . It wasn 't me who kicked you . It was Ter .
Shake him off .
Come on .
Hurry ... hurry .
Paddle harder . We 're not moving .
Faster . Damn it !
Paddling with our hands to escape is no use .
Here you go .
I will paddle .
I will do it .
Give it your best Ter ! Row .
why don 't you keep rowing ?
why did you stop ?
keep rowing . Hey hurry .
Aey will catch up to us .
What is it now ?
Ter don 't stand up . The boat will flip over .
What the hell ?
Ter ?
move .
What ?
Me too ? Yeah you move aside .
Which way ? Right .
Fine .
Only Puak ? Shin you move left .
Left . My left or your left .
Just pick one !
Which side ? Whichever left side .
Whose left side ?
The left hand side that you use to wipe your ass !
Which way ? My wound hurts .
Mak did you move back for what !
Move . Move where ?
Move right . Okay .
move to the left . Left .
Which way ? Move whatever way .
Which side . Which side ? I What ?
Gosh damn . Put your head down .
Get your head down to your feet ! Hurry ! Down farther .
Gosh I 'm sore now .
Gosh !
The drums of war sound off like rolling thunder as we set out to protect our homeland .
Why are you singing now ?
I know .
And why am I dancing along ?
Roused to the point of release I raise my white flag in sweet surrender .
I bust a rag out and just polish the sword . Yay !
Nak is the ghost !
Let 's
come on !
Mak !
Me too .
Mak ! Come on . Let 's go .
Let 's go .
hurry .
Give me your hand . Ter ! Come on .
Mak hurry UP !
Mak !
jump now !
now ! just jump !
Shin
just jump !
jump !
I told you I can 't swim .
Just jump now .
Shin
Shin jump ! Now hurry up .
Help me . Hey come on .
Didn 't you say you cannot swim .
Gosh your stroke is like Michael Phelps !
Nak !
get out of here .
I am not going .
You crazy . Sorry .
What 's up with that ? That hurts !
How come you didn 't pass out ?
In the movies I see they do this and they always pass out .
What the hell is wrong with you !
Puak
Is he dead ? I don 't know .
Just drag him away . Run hurry ...
Run run ...
Let 's go .
father ?
no matter what happens .
Do not step outside the enchanted thread .
People aren 't donating very much nowadays .
We 've been waiting for months to get it fixed .
Father !
I almost shit my pants .
Now I do .
what 's next ?
Don 't worry . I will handle this .
Nak
don 't !
baby .
Don 't listen to her .
Gosh you 're a ghost
stop with the sweet talk already !
please do what you have to .
Ter
Please give me the holy water .
Don 't hurt my wife .
Don 't . Don 't hurt my wife . Let me go !
Nak !
Do it father . Pee Mak .
Please help me .
don 't ! Nak .
Nak
Let me go .
Damn Ter
You spilled it all . It 's okay .
please give me the holy rice .
Let me go .
Nak .
Shin . Nak .
Chirping ... chirping .
so tame . Eating from my palm .
Why not try eating from my feet then !
This isn 't the time to go all animal lover on us .
That 's okay .
As long as we stay inside the holy thread . We will be safe .
Father !
What the heck ? ! Whose hand is it ?
Shit ! Which way to go ? !
Shin ?
What 's up with this ?
It 's time for me to go .
Gosh ! The monk already made it over the wall .
Turn the other way . I 'm getting the creeps .
Hurry . Nak
Pee Mak Nak
Pee Mak
Gosh that 's enough already !
This isn 't some name calling game .
Let 's go that way .
Aey !
please let us go . We used to be friends .
you know .
Ter ! You 're the one who kicked him off the boat . I told you not to !
I 'm not a ghost .
I don 't believe you . Don 't come any closer .
Don 't push !
Nak !
Ter ?
you are still wet right ?
Of course . Why ?
Shin . Mak
I will count to 3 and push Puak towards Aey now .
One Can we talk about this first ?
Two Shit .
Three . I hate you all .
Everyone jump him . Jump for what !
See ? If you are still human why did you scream when the holy water touched you ?
I screamed because you guys are on top of me and it hurts !
Disgusting !
Come on . Get up . Get up .
Get up .
So why does the holy water not hurt you like Nak ?
I told you I am not a ghost .
How come you got the ring ?
Well ...
I needed some money .
I saw with my own eyes that the ruby ring is exactly like Nak 's .
Is the Ruby big ?
Where is Aey ?
Aey ?
I had diarrhea .
I 'm sorry
I needed the money to gamble .
I had you all wrong . I am sorry .
I thought you were a ghost .
But actually
You are a casino junkie .
And you watching too many movies and always making presumptions .
Are you guys forgetting something ?
What ?
That Nak is still standing here ?
Nak
let 's go . Run !
Let 's go .
It 's stuck .
This one is stuck too .
Gosh Nak
Please just let us go .
You are a ghost so stay in your own world .
You cannot be with the living .
It 's unnatural . It 's sacrilegious .
It won 't work out . It 's not OK .
Can 't you understand ?
Don 't mess with me !
What happened ?
Nak disappeared .
It 's stuck too .
What are we going to do ?
I will donate a lot of money
to fix this damn roof !
Puak
it 's not the roof .
run !
Nak
please don 't hurt us . I 'm really scared .
Even in your normal form I 'm already scared shitless .
Now with your head upside down like Spiderman .
Why do you keep getting between Pee Mak and I ?
What have I ever done to you ?
Because you are an evil ghost !
Why did you kill aunty Priek ?
I didn 't kill her .
fell in the water and drown by herself .
I don 't believe you .
Beautiful yet a big fat liar !
I told you . I didn 't kill her .
Let 's
I just wanted to be with the person I love .
Why do you guys have to get in the way ?
This isn 't called love . It 's called selfishness .
Right . Mak can 't go anywhere anymore
The townsfolk are all scared of him .
I am scared too .
Why don 't you go where you 're supposed to go ?
Just like Mak 's aunty . She didn 't come back .
Neither did aunty Priek .
They 've probably been reincarnated and are married already .
You died already . How can you be with Mak ?
If I can 't be with Mak in this world
Then Pee Mak must go with me .
What the hell are you standing there for ?
Mak
Are you that scared of me ?
I am so sorry ...
If I ever hurt you
I wouldn 't be able to live with myself .
Don 't cry baby .
You won 't look handsome .
I am so sorry
for lying to you all this time .
I just wanted to be with you as long as I could .
Even if it 's just for one more day .
Do you still remember what we talked about on the ferris wheel ?
I am sorry
you can 't get to die before me .
Please promise me
When I am gone .
You will have to carry on .
Nak ...
You don 't have to go anywhere .
You said you lied to me .
You didn 't lie to me at all .
Even though I am a fool .
But I am not so stupid that I wouldn 't know that my wife is dead .
I will go send off your friends .
Nak
What did you do
to get this dirty ?
Let 's see what my darling prepared for me to eat .
Your cooking is as good as always .
Nak my love you are too pretty
to be a ghost .
Right ?
I realized it since we 're playing charades .
Even if all the townsfolk avoid me
and nobody wanted to be my friend .
And even if I have to eat dried leave everyday .
I would still want to be with you .
Thank you
but it is impossible .
Why not ?
We can just pretend that nothing has changed .
All this time we did fine together .
But I 'm dead .
The living and the dead
can 't stay together . It 's not natural .
If that 's so
then my love for you is also a freak of nature .
When I was at war .
Do you have any last words ?
I should have died that day .
No one thought I would make it .
But I found my way back to you .
Help
Pee Mak
Even you died already
but was still able to come back for me .
You also used your powers to help me hit those cans .
So we could bring a doll back for Dang .
How is it wrong
that we can love each other this much ?
Aren 't you scared of me ?
You know I am terrified of ghosts .
But I am more terrified of living without you .
Just one thing though .
Don 't ever hang upside down
like that again .
I almost had a heart attack .
Damn
I am really moved .
I promise you
no matter what happens
we will be friends forever .
Yeah
If you die and become ghosts
I won 't be afraid .
But I remember you kicked me off the boat .
Come on
Love you .
Nak ...
Do you love me ?
I do .
How much ?
Nak loves Pee Mak a lot lot lot .
I love you
heaps heaps heaps too .
There 's more ...
Nak
I need more time to look at each other
I wish I could freeze the moment
forever before we must part .
I love you .
Give me your hand to hold and to keep my heart warm
Let me look in your eyes so I will never be lonely
Let me have your love to inspire me to make my dreams come true .
father .
Let us know if there is anything else we can help .
baby .
Be careful of your hand .
What ?
Horn ?
Hair ?
You ? She ?
Does she mean head ? Yeah ?
There is head in the phrase . Watermelon head ?
Exploding head ? Potato head ?
What kind of head ?
Air head ?
Headless ?
Headless . Pee Mak is correct !
Yayyy !
This is the first time I got it right .
Shin
aren 't you happy for me ?
Haunted house . Scarier than ever .
Play with me .
Wow . So very realistic .
I know .
Thank you .
Come on . Hurry up .
Watch this .
You 'll never hit the target . You throw like a blind man .
This time don 't help me ok ?
Everybody
Mak has really gone too far .
Yeah !
We can 't let this kind of unnatural go on in our village .
Yeah ! We can 't allow it !
No way !
Tonight I will get rid of it .
Anyone coming with me ?
Yeah !
I want to go too .
Shit .
Better hurry before you miss out .
Go on . Hurry up .